

# **SUMMARY**

# Web Developer,

Develops mainly using React.js (with and without Hooks) with Redux, vanilla JavaScript and Node.js.

Passionate about solving daily challenges, with experience in the latest web technologies.

Can build a full-scale web app from PSD to a live responsive page.

# **CONTACT ME**

Phone:

054-4594273

#### Portfolio:

https://rotemyehiel.github.io/rotempatrakeev-portfolio/

#### LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/rotempatrakeev-143608163/

#### Fmail:

rotem8y@gmail.com

#### **HOBBIES**

Baking Traveling

#### **LANGUAGES**

Hebrew- Native English- High level

# **ARMY SERVICE**

2010-2012

Computers Corps Commander and instructor of encryption courses.

# ROTEM PATRAKEEV

# Web Developer

# **EDUCATION**

# Coding Academy (Mister bit bootcamp)

January 2020 - May 2020

Web development course (Full Stack)

### Holon Institute of Technology (HIT)

2015-2019

<u>B.Sc. Technology Management</u> -Information Systems Management and Development.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Karma shopping (startup company)- Frontend developer

2022-today

Developing and enhancing our main web application using React.js (Hooks) with Redux and vanilla JavaScript, with expertise in creating responsive designs using flexbox.

Developed web extensions and website integrated into the main product.

#### YIT- Frontend developer

2021-2022

Build desktop and responsive web apps using React.js, TypeScript and vanilla lavaScript.

In addition, Responsible from end-to-end for a main product from development to deployment.

# Adworks Ltd- Full stack developer

2020-2021

Build a Next, React, Node.js apps from scratch such as: ecommerce app, scrapping app and chrome extension.

#### **Marmanet- Data Coordinator**

2019

Comparison and concentration of data.

#### N & J Industrial Food Machinery LTD

2015-2019

Responsibility for the company's website-

Editing HTML, and marketing the web using Google Ads and Google Analytics, making technical support and orders.

#### **TECH SKILLS**

#### **Programing:**

JavaScript (ES6), HTML5, CSS3, SASS, TypeScript, Server with Node.js.

# Frameworks:

Next, Vue, Express.

#### Data manage:

MongoDB, SQL Server.

# Libraries:

React, Jest, JSDOM, Storybook, Bootstrap, Webpack, jQuery, Redux, Ajax, Axios and Font awesome.